A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Art, Series C FA340
Rockefeller Archive Center
- CKU Reference Files, 1949-1979; 3; 27.6 Cubic Feet
  - Smith, Ralph - Smyth (Box 57, Folder 486)
    Smith, Ralph B. Smith, Shirlann Smith, Tony Smithsonian (re Carl Fox) Smith, Violet O. Smith, William S. Smithsonian Associates Women's Committee Smithsonian Smithsonian Institution National Air and Space Museum Smyth, Craig
  - Smith, Ralph - Smyth (Box 57, Folder 0486A)
  - Snelling - Sommerfeld (Box 57, Folder 487)
    Snelling, John Snodgrass, Mrs. Idell Snow, Mrs. Abraham Snow, Fred Snow, Gordon Snyder, John L. Snyder, Marjorie Soble, John J. Society for the Renewal of Christian Art, The Soderblom, J.E. Soiken, Corinne (Mrs. R. Weinberg) Solinger, Janet Solomon and Company Fine Art Solovij, Jurij Sokoloff, Sergius Sommerfeld, Mrs. J.J.
  - Snelling - Sommerfeld (Box 57, Folder 0487A)
  - Sorce - Sowinski (Box 57, Folder 488)
    Sorce, Marie J. Soremy, E.V. Sosnowitz, Henry Sotheby Sotheby Parke Bernet Sotheby Catalogue Order Forms Sotheby & Co., London Soucy, Jean South Mall Project Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art Southampton Art Gallery Southampton East Sowinski, Mrs. Jan
  - Sorce - Sowinski (Box 57, Folder 0488A)
    Southworth, Eleanor
  - Space World Creations - Spanier (Box 57, Folder 489)
    Space World Creations Spaced Spadey, Francis X. Spanier, Joseph J.
  - Spanish-American Painters - Spanish Pavilion (New York World's Fair) (Box 57, Folder 490)
    Spanish-American Painters and Sculptors, Inc. Spanish Institute Spanish Pavilion - New York's World's Fair
  - Spanish Pavilion (New York World's Fair) - Spanish Works of Art (Box 57, Folder 491)
    Spanish Pavilion - NY World's Fair Spanish Works of Art
  - Spaulding - Squires (Box 57, Folder 492)
    Spaulding, Douglas M. Special Destiny Women in America Spector, Naomi Speelman, Jules (A.J. Speelman, Ltd.) Spencer, Louis Speyer, Darthea (Galerie Darthea Spencer) Spillius, James Spira, B. Spivey, George Spoor, Louis Sprinkle, Mrs. Bruce T. Spurkel, Herman Spurlock, Clarence E. Squires, Norma Jean
  - Staatsgalerie Stuttgart - Staempfli Gallery (Box 57, Folder 493)
    Staatsgalerie Stuttgart Staempfi Gallery
  - Staatsgalerie Stuttgart - Staempfli Gallery (Box 57, Folder 0493A)
  - Stafford - Startup (Box 57, Folder 494)
    Stafford, Roland L. Stahl, Wilma Stahler, H.A. Stahly, Francois Stake, Paul W. Stanley, Bob Stark, Margaret Stark, Mary Stark, William and Company Startup, Peter
  - State Museum at Albany - State University of New York at Albany (Box 58, Folder 495)
    State Museum at Albany State of New York State University of New York at Albany
  - State University of New York at Albany - Stavisky (Box 58, Folder 496)
    State University of New York at Albany State University of New York at Alfred State University of New York at Fredonia State University of New York, Harpur College State University of New York at Purchase Stavenhagen, Kurt Stavisky, Lotta
  - Steadman - Stephenson (Box 58, Folder 497)
    Steadman, William E. Stearn, Gerald Stebbins, Mrs. S. Stec, Genovieve Stec, Andrew and Mattias Stefanelli, Joseph Stein, Mrs. William Steiner, Josef Steiner, Paul Steinhauer, Esther M. Stendahl, Earl L. Earl Stendahl Gallery Stenfield, Larry Stephenson, Malvina Stephenson, Roger Stephenson, Virginia
  - Sterling - Stockman (Box 58, Folder 498)
    Sterling, Julian A. Stern, Harold P. Stern, Jan Peter Stern, Max Sterns, Marcia Stevenson, Victoria Cheyne Stewart, Augustus R. Stewart, D.W. Stewart, Ethel M. Stewart, Hannah Stewart, Robert Sticky Wax Stix, Adine H. Stockman, Captain Meyer
  - Stojanovich - Storrs (Box 58, Folder 499)
    Stojanovich, Anna Stolfa, Lucille Stoller, John C. Stoltman, Alan Stone, Mrs. Albert Stone, Al Stone, Allan Allan Stone Galleries Stone, Mary E. Stone, Norma W. Stone, Sylvia Stooshnoff, Paul W. Stopinski, Daniel Storm King Art Center Storrs, John S.
  - Streiff - Stuurman (Box 58, Folder 500)
    Streiff, Bruno Stretton, Robert H. Strider, Marjorie V. Strimple, Mrs. Virgil E. Strong, Brett - Livingstone Strong, Charles H. Strong, R.E. Stronneillo, Olga Stout, Miss E. Burdell Strunks, Ralph E. Stuart, Gilbert Studio Museum Harlem Studly, Adolph (Adolph Studly Inc.) Stuurman, Phyllis
  - Streiff - Stuurman (Box 58, Folder 0500A)
  - Sudanese - Suntory Museum of Art (Box 58, Folder 501)
    Sudanese Sculpture Sugino, Shizu Sugiyura Sulkis, Karl D. Sullins, Maurice Sullivan, John G. Sullivan, William D. Summers, Mrs. Rickie Summit Gallery Suntory Museum of Art Sullivan, Max
  - Sustersic - Suzuki (Box 58, Folder 502)
    Sutherland, Agnes S. Sutherland, Bruce D. Sutra, Israel Suttman, Paul Suydam, Connie Suzuki, Shizuo
  - Sustersic - Suzuki (Box 58, Folder 0502A)
    Sustersic, Teresa F.
  - Swain - Szyk (Box 58, Folder 503)
    Swain, J. Grover Swain, Robert Swatzell, Nola Sylva, M.S. Syracuse Szabo, Steve Szabo, Irene E. Szarvady, J. Szasz, Frank Szeredas, Jeno Szolich, Martha Szyk, Arthur
  - Swain - Szyk (Box 58, Folder 0503A)
    Swan, Paul
  - Sales, 1969-1977 (Box 59, Folder 504)
    Memoranda re questions about items to be sold. Auction catalogs. Lists of NAR artworks to be sold.
  - Sales, 1969-1977 (Box 59, Folder 0504A)
  - Sales, 1969-1977 (Box 59, Folder 505)
  - Sales, 1969-1977 (Box 59, Folder 0505A)
  - Screen/Scroll Conservation/Restoration, 1975-1977 (Box 59, Folder 506)
    Memoranda and receipts for restoration work.
  - Stein Exhibit, 1969-1971 (Box 59, Folder 507)
    Memoranda, lists and catalogs from "Four Americans in Paris," an exhibit of Gertrude Stein's paintings. NAR lent paintings. Exhibit arranged by Museum of Modern Art (MoMA).
  - Stein Exhibit, 1969-1971 (Box 59, Folder 0507A)
  - Stein Exhibit, 1969-1971 (Box 59, Folder 508)
  - Stein Exhibit, 1969-1971 (Box 59, Folder 0508A)
  - Stone Conservation/Restoration, 1951, 1969-1976 (Box 59, Folder 509)
    Correspondence, memoranda and background on products and processes used in stone conservation.
  - Stone Conservation/Restoration, 1951, 1969-1976 (Box 59, Folder 510)
  - Stone, Kykuit, 1951, 1969-1972 (Box 59, Folder 511)
    Memoranda re products and processes to be used for conservation projects at Kykuit.
  - Storage, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 512)
    Memoranda re storage of NAR fine arts in humidity controlled warehouse. Contract included.
  - Storage, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 0512A)
  - Tables - Tapestry Associates (Box 60, Folder 514)
    Tables, Elephant Table, ivory table Kykiut Tacccola, Umberto Tacha, Athena Tack, Rose Taheri, Joseph Takeuchi, Zenichiro Taksa, Isak Talbot, Clare Talkington, William Talmey, Allene Tamayo, Rufino Tancreto, Evelyn Tanglewood Press, Inc. Tanis, Mrs. J. Tannenbaum, Thelma Tanner, Allen Tanner, Stephen Tanner, Virginia Tapestries Tapestry Associates
  - Tapiador - Taylor (Box 60, Folder 515)
    Tapiador, Prisco Tappan, Rory C. Tarbell, Roberta K. Tarrytown (photos of furniture returned from Washington, D.C.) Tavel, Ron Tawes, Cleonice F. Taylor, Esther A. Taylor, George Taylor, Henry Fitch Taylor, James Taylor, James E. II Taylor, Ralph W. Taylor, Robert Taylor, Rose
  - Tapiador - Taylor (Box 60, Folder 0515A)
  - Teater - Texana (Box 60, Folder 516)
    Teater, Archie B. Temple Beth El, Rochester, N.Y. Temple B'Nai Shalom Tenney, Marietta Ternet, G. Terri, Amanda Terruso, Saverio Terry, Lamar Teruel, Octavio Tervuren Magazine Tesch, J. Tessmer, L.A. Texana
  - Teater - Texana (Box 60, Folder 0516A)
  - Thannhauser - Thornton (Box 60, Folder 517)
    Thannhauser, J.K. Thaw, E.V. The, Mrs. T. Theberge, Giselle Thedford, Richard Theriault, Gerard Thoma, Richard and Marna Thomas, E.C. Thomas, Mrs. S.O. Thompson, Jean Thompson, R.L. Thompson, Sarah E. J. Walter Thompson Company Thorton, Mrs. Charles
  - Thrupp - Titlebaum (Box 60, Folder 518)
    Thrupp, Mrs. Iona Thuman, Rosemary Thurston, Doris J. Tibbetts, Joan Crosby Tibor de Nagy Gallery Tidd House Murals Tierney, Charles Tiger, George E. Tilleux, Frances Tillman, Hazel King Time, Inc. Time-Life Records Sunday Times Magazine Tinley, Mrs. H.L. Tinoco Hijo, Pedro R. Titarenko, Oleg Titen, Beatrice L. Titlebaum, Richard
  - Tobey - Towers (Box 60, Folder 519)
    Tobey, Alton S. Todd, Michael P. Todd, Ruth Toffel, Al Tokyo World's Fair Tolegian, Manuel J. Toms River Yacht Club Tonetti Tonner, Leslie Topping, Mabel T. Topping, Mrs. William Hayes Towner, Kathleen Toral, Cristobal Toronto, The Art Gallery of Torres, Mrs. Henry Torres, R. Castro Touchstone Gallery Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri Tour, President of Guinea Towers, Frank J.
  - Trajkovic - Tsujimoto (Box 60, Folder 520)
    Trajkovic, Vladimir Trampetti, James J. Trauscht, Bernard J. Treen, Mabel E. Trentinian, Arnold Triton Press, Inc. Trizna, Alexandra Tronerud, Norman K. Trova Troxelle, Margaret Troyan, Matthew Truex, Vanday Truman, Jacques Truman, Jock Tsolson, Mr. and Mrs. Vissilios Tsou, Peter Tsujimoto, Kanya
  - Trajkovic - Tsujimoto (Box 60, Folder 0520A)
  - Tuchman - Tumarkin (Box 60, Folder 521)
    Tuchman, Maurice Tukamoto, S. Tuller, Mrs. Edwin H. Tumarkin, Igael
  - Turken - Tyson (Box 60, Folder 522)
    Turken, Francene Turman, Suzanna Joy Turner, Carolyn D. Turner, Joseph H. Turrenne des Pres, F. Turville, William S. Tuttle, Mrs. Macowin Tuttman, Saul T.V. Program - "Proud Possessors" Tweel, Bill Twentieth Century Club Twentyman, Esther Tyschper, Margaret Tyson, Stephen D.
  - Turken - Tyson (Box 60, Folder 0522A)
    Turner, Howard
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit, 1949, 1955-1969 (Box 60, Folder 524)
    Memoranda and notes re storage, placement and maintenance of artwork at Kykuit. Architectural drawings for storage room.
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit, 1949, 1955-1969 (Box 60, Folder 0524A)
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit, 1970-1973 (Box 61, Folder 525)
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit, 1970-1973 (Box 61, Folder 0525A)
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit, 1974-1975 (Box 61, Folder 526)
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit, 1976-1977 (Box 61, Folder 527)
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit, 1976-1977 (Box 61, Folder 0527A)
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit - Lists/Maps of Galleries and Outdoor Sculpture - Masters and Drafts, 1968-1980 (Box 61, Folder 528)
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit - Lists/Maps of Galleries and Outdoor Sculpture - Masters and Drafts, 1968-1980 (Box 61, Folder 529)
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit - Lists/Maps of Galleries and Outdoor Sculpture - Masters and Drafts, 1968-1980 (Box 61, Folder 530)
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit - Lists/Maps of Galleries and Outdoor Sculpture, 1969-1977 (Box 62, Folder 531)
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit - Other, 1970-1977 (Box 62, Folder 532)
    Memoranda and notes re Mexican Folk Art shelving behind Greenrock, storage in barn, fireplace in the playhouse.
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit - Other, 1970-1977 (Box 62, Folder 0532A)
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit - Outdoors, 1970-1977 (Box 62, Folder 533)
    Memoranda re maintenance and care of sculpture at Kykuit.
  - Tarrytown - Kykuit - Outdoors, 1970-1977 (Box 62, Folder 0533A)
  - Teheran, Museum of Contemporary Arts, 1976-1977 (Box 62, Folder 534)
    Correspondence, memoranda and background material re prints given to the Shah of Iran by NAR in 1976 and an exhibition of the prints.
  - Teheran, Museum of Contemporary Arts, 1976-1977 (Box 62, Folder 535)
  - Teheran, Museum of Contemporary Arts, 1976-1977 (Box 62, Folder 536)
  - Textile Conservation/Restoration, 1967, 1972-1977 (Box 62, Folder 537)
    Memorandum and notes re cleaning of silks and tapestries.
  - Transportation Office Forms, 1969-1971 (Box 62, Folder 538)
    Forms stating item to be transported, location removed from and taken to and scheduled date of transport. Receipts for items picked up and received.
  - Transportation Office Forms, January 1972 - June 1972 (Box 62, Folder 539)
  - Transportation Office Forms, July 1972 - December 1972 (Box 62, Folder 540)
  - Transportation Office Forms, July 1972 - December 1972 (Box 62, Folder 0540A)
  - Transportation Office Forms, January 1973 - June 1973 (Box 63, Folder 541)
  - Transportation Office Forms, July 1973 - December 1973 (Box 63, Folder 542)
  - Transportation Office Forms, July 1973 - December 1973 (Box 63, Folder 0542A)
  - Transportation Office Forms, January 1974 - June 1974 (Box 63, Folder 543)
  - Transportation Office Forms, January 1974 - June 1974 (Box 63, Folder 0543A)
  - Transportation Office Forms, July 1974 - December 1974 (Box 63, Folder 544)
  - Transportation Office Forms, July 1974 - December 1974 (Box 63, Folder 0544A)
  - Transportation Office Forms, January 1975 - June 1975 (Box 63, Folder 545)
  - Transportation Office Forms, January 1975 - June 1975 (Box 63, Folder 0545A)
  - Transportation Office Forms, July 1975 - December 1975 (Box 63, Folder 546)
  - Transportation Office Forms, July 1975 - December 1975 (Box 63, Folder 0546A)
  - Transportation Office Forms, January 1976 - March 1976 (Box 63, Folder 547)
  - Transportation Office Forms, April 1976 - June 1976 (Box 64, Folder 548)
  - Transportation Office Forms, July 1976 - August 1976 (Box 64, Folder 549)
  - Transportation Office Forms, September 1976 - October 1976 (Box 64, Folder 550)
  - Transportation Office Forms, November 1976 - December 1976 (Box 64, Folder 551)
  - Transportation Office Forms, November 1976 - December 1976 (Box 64, Folder 0551A)
  - Transportation Office Forms, January 1977 - February 1977 (Box 64, Folder 552)
  - Transportation Office Forms, January 1977 - February 1977 (Box 64, Folder 0552A)
  - Transportation Office Forms, March 1977 (Box 64, Folder 553)
  - Transportation Office Forms, March 1977 (Box 64, Folder 0553A)
  - Transportation Office Forms, April 1977 - June 1977 (Box 64, Folder 554)
  - Transportation Office Forms, April 1977 - June 1977 (Box 64, Folder 0554A)
  - Transportation Office Forms, July 1977 - September 1977 (Box 64, Folder 555)
  - Transportation Office Forms, July 1977 - September 1977 (Box 64, Folder 0555A)
  - Transportation Office Forms, October 1977 - December 1977 (Box 64, Folder 556)
  - Transportation Office Forms, October 1977 - December 1977 (Box 64, Folder 0556A)
  - Transportation Office Forms, January 1978 - February 1978 (Box 65, Folder 557)
  - Transportation Office Forms, March 1978 - June 1978 (Box 65, Folder 558)
  - Trip by NAR and Mrs. Rockefeller - General, Paris, Iran, Australia, Tunisia, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 559)
    Background information on the trip. Basic information re each location. Letters of introduction.
  - Trip by NAR and Mrs. Rockefeller - General, Paris, Iran, Australia, Tunisia, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 0559A)
  - Trip by NAR and Mrs. Rockefeller - General, Paris, Iran, Australia, Tunisia, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 560)
  - Trip by NAR and Mrs. Rockefeller - General, Paris, Iran, Australia, Tunisia, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 0560A)
  - Trip by NAR and Mrs. Rockefeller - Points of Interest, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 561)
    Recommended places to visit at each location. These are divided into things to do in the time allotted and only if time allows.
  - Trip by NAR and Mrs. Rockefeller - Points of Interest, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 0561A)
  - Uber - United Nations (Box 65, Folder 562)
    Uber, Mrs. James D. UCLA Frederick S. Wright Art Gallery Udvardy, Zoltan Uht, John Ulicny, John James Ulrich, Mrs. L.J. Underwood, Garnett Union Church, Pocantico United Hospital Fund United Jewish Appeal United Nations Association of San Francisco
  - Uber - United Nations (Box 65, Folder 0562A)
  - University of Arizona - Uzunoglu (Box 65, Folder 563)
    University of Arizona University Art Museum, Berkley, California University of Hartford University of Pennsylvania, University Museum University of South Africa University of Texas University of Washington Upchurch, Mrs. W.W. Upton, Lucy Upton, Richard Uris, Norman Ursus Books, Ltd. U.S. Government Printing Office Uzunoglu, Derman
  - Vaci - Van Hoeydonck (Box 65, Folder 564)
    Vaci, Maria Valentine, Mary C.B. Vallance, Malcolm W. Valtat Van der Aa, Hans Van Der Heijden, L.N. Vander Horst, Pam VanderJagt, L. Van der Made de Tielens, Evelyn Van der marck, Jan Vandervort, Helen Vanderwef, Sydney Van der Weyden, Rogier Van Derzee, Leslie Van de Sande, Theodore Van Doesburg, Madame Petro Van Donger, Kees Van Fossen, Arnold Van Gilder, Edmund Van Hamel, Mrs. Manette Van Hoeydonck
  - Van Ness - Vazifdar (Box 65, Folder 565)
    Van Ness, Mrs. Robert P. van Ryckeiorsel-Paulues, Jeanne Van Veen, Stuyvesant Van Wye, William J. Vargas, Mawy Vargas, Pedro Varga-Sinka, Michael Vassar College Art Gallery Vazifdar, J.P.
  - Van Ness - Vazifdar (Box 65, Folder 0565A)
  - Veazey - Veydras (Box 66, Folder 566)
    Veazey, Raymond Veerhoff, Otto Vega, Marta Vehrlin, Voldemar Veisse, Jeannine Vela, Bettina Velmar, Andre Vencius, Victoria Veydras, Ltd. Veneziano, Domenico Venezuela Venice Biennale Ver Duft, Lee Verlop, Caroline Vermersch, Maurice L. Vermonte, Rosa Vetter, Mr. and Mrs. Elmer F. Veydras, Ltd.
  - Veazey - Veydras (Box 66, Folder 0566A)
  - Vice Presidential Inaugural Medal - Vincent (Box 66, Folder 567)
    Vice Presidential Inaugural Medal Victor, Mary O'Neill Victoria & Albert Museum, London Vigtel, Gudmund Viking Press Vincent, Tom Villalaz, Candida de Vincent, Mrs. Clark E.
  - Vice Presidential Inaugural Medal - Vincent (Box 66, Folder 0567A)
    Vienna
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts - Vlaminck (Box 66, Folder 568)
    Virginia Museum of Fine Arts Virtanen, John O. Vita, Anna Viviano, Catherine (Catherine Viviano Gallery) Vlaminck
  - Vogel - Volunteer (Box 66, Folder 569)
    Vogel Van and Storage Vogelsanger, Mrs. E.E. Vogt, Richard Vogue Magazine Voice-Lovsky, Michael Vojislav, Stamenic Volechenisky, Mike Volunteer Service Photographers
  - Vogel - Volunteer (Box 66, Folder 0569A)
  - von Barghahn - Vreeland (Box 66, Folder 570)
    von Barghahn, Mildred Von Friedeberg, Elsa Von Koch, Mrs. Isolde Von Oelschlaeger, Alfred von Schelling, Hermann Von Schoeler, Baron W.V. Von Stach, Helena Von Thun, Jack Vorbusch, Rudolph O. Vose Galleries of Boston (Robert C. Bose Jr.) Vreeland, Elizabeth W.
  - Valentin Gallery, 1951-1954, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 571)
    Correspondence re purchases by NAR.
  - Venezuela, 1963-1966, 1972, 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder 572)
    Correspondence and memoranda re NAR's art at Monte Sacro.
  - Venezuela, 1963-1966, 1972, 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder 0572A)
  - Waddell Gallery - Waikiki (Box 66, Folder 573)
    Waddell Gallery Waddell, Gene Wade, Jane (Jade Wade Ltd.) Wadsworth Atheneum Wager, Ann Wagner, G. Noble Waikiki, Hyatt Regency
  - Waddell Gallery - Waikiki (Box 66, Folder 0573A)
  - Waldner - Wang (Box 66, Folder 574)
    Waldner, Raymond Waldorf-Astoria, The Waldron, Mrs. A.W. Walker Art Center, Minneapolis Walker Street Gallery Wallace, W.H. Wallace, Walter Wallis, David Wally, George Walsh, Betty Walsh, Patrick A. Walter, Emile Walter, Kennith L. Walters Art Gallery Walter's Electric Picture lights Walters, Ernest Walters, Winter Wands, Robert A. Wang, Tom
  - Ward - Wasey (Box 66, Folder 575)
    Ward, Edna R. Ward, Kennith R. Ward, Lyle Ward-Nasse Gallery Ward, Mrs. Wyn Ware, Mrs. Malcolm Wariko, M. Washaw, Monroe Wasey, Jane
  - Washburn - Washington State University (Box 66, Folder 576)
    Washburn, Edward G. Washburn, Joan Washburn Gallery Washburn, Mrs. Newell R. Washington, D.C., The National Gallery Washington, David Washington Gallery of Modern Art Washington, Grace L. Washington International Art Letter Washington Performing Arts Society Washington, State of Washington State University Museum of Art
  - Wasser - Way (Box 67, Folder 577)
    Wasser, Jacques Wasson, Ben Waterhouse, Joy C. Watherston, Margaret Watkins, Bessie Watson, Eve Watzik Wave Hill Waverly Gallery, Inc. Way, Fred
  - WBFO - Weddle (Box 67, Folder 578)
    WBFO WCNY-TV Weathers, Beverly Weathers, Mrs. O.J. Weaver, Alma Weaver, J.H. Weber, Mrs. Aerme Weber, Bruce Weber, Mrs. John D. Weber, John Gallery Webster, Edward B. Weddell, Richard Weddle, Don
  - Wedgwood - Weidner (Box 67, Folder 579)
    Wedgwood, Mrs. J. Dean Weening, Hugo Wehrlin, Voldemar Wehrmal, Helen Weidenfeld and Nicolson Weidner, Roswell and Marilyn
  - Weill - Weitzenhoffer (Box 67, Folder 580)
    Weill, Pierre-Andre Weil, Andre Weinman, Robert A. Weimann, Robert P. Jr. Weinberg, H.P. Weinberg, Herbert Weinberg, Margie Blake Weiner, Elizabeth Weingrow, Howard Weinmuller, A. Weintraub Gallery Weinzierl, Mrs. George Weisbrich, Alfred L. Weitzen, Elaine G. Weitzenhoffer, A. Max
  - Weill - Weitzenhoffer (Box 67, Folder 0580A)
  - Weld - Werboff (Box 67, Folder 581)
    Weld, Anne F. Wellesley College Welliver, Neil Wells, Catherine Wells, Charles Wells, Mrs. Henry H. Wells, Joseph H. Welter, Roger J. Wenger, Elisabeth Wenger, Joseph Werboff, Michel
  - Werboff - Wetzel (Box 67, Folder 582)
    Werboff, Michel West, Harriette E. West, Peter B. Westbeth Westchester Art Society Westchester Arts Council Westhaver, J.L. Wetzel, Richard
  - Werboff - Wetzel (Box 67, Folder 0582A)
    Westcott, Mrs. C. Jr.
  - Whanki - Whiteman (Box 67, Folder 583)
    Whanki, Mr. Kim Wharton, Dolores Wheaton College Wheeler, Judy E. Wheeler, Monroe Wheeler, Mrs. Walter Wheelock, George L. Wheelwright Museum Whipple, Enez Whitbeck, Joan Whitcomb, Kay White, Arch White, Carol White, Cecilia White, Colin White, Mrs. Edward B. White, Elzie White, Walter S. Whiteman, Andrew
  - Whanki - Whiteman (Box 67, Folder 0583A)
  - Whitman - Whitney (Box 67, Folder 584)
    Whitman, Colden H. Whitman College Whitmarsh, Mrs. Leonard Whitmore, Sidney R. Whitney Museum of American Art Whitney Museum Auction Whitney Galleries of New York
  - Whitman - Whitney (Box 67, Folder 0584A)
  - Wick - Willard (Box 67, Folder 585)
    Wick, Mrs. George Wiederanders, Dr. and Mrs. Rex Wieder, Howard Weisner, E. Wigder Gallery of Modern Art Wiggins, Guy Wightman, K.R. Wikoff, Mr. and Mrs. J. Allen Wilburne, Ella Wilcox, Dorothy Wilczyk, M. Wilde, John Wildenstein & Co. Will, Dennis Willard, Marion Willard Gallery
  - Williams - Wilson (Box 67, Folder 586)
    Williams, Edna Williams, The Honerable Jack, Governor of Arizona Williams, Mrs. John M. Willis, Carl R. Willoughby, Bob Wills, A.A. and Sons Willson, Robert Willson, Ruth D. Wilson, Al Wilson, Joseph C. Memorial Fund Wilson, Malcolm Wilson, Lois Wilson, Mark
  - Williams - Wilson (Box 67, Folder 0586A)
    Williams, Mrs. M.R. Wilson, A.L. Wilson, Marguerite
  - Wiltsey - Winters (Box 68, Folder 587)
    Wiltsey, Ralph Windels, Mrs. Richard Windhorst, H.M. Window Shop, The Windsor & Company Winingger, H.E. Winrock Farm Winston, Diana Winston, Martine Winterbottom, William Wirtz, Virginia Wadsworth Winters, Winifred
  - Wise Gallery - WMHT (Box 68, Folder 588)
    Wise, Howard Gallery Wise, John Wiseman, Mrs. Matthew WITCO Chemical Co. Witheridge, Marian I. Withers, Josephine Witt, F.A. Wittenborn Wittenborn Books WMHT -TV
  - Woffard - Wolther (Box 68, Folder 589)
    Woffard, J.C. Wolfe Art Club (Catherine Lorillard) Wolfram, William R. Wolfson, Lisa M. Wolkin, Mrs. Paul Wolther, Lawrence I.
  - Woffard - Wolther (Box 68, Folder 0589A)
  - "Woman's Day" - Woodworth (Box 68, Folder 590)
    Woman's Day Woman's Club of Pocantico Hills Women's Council of the Rochester Memorial Art Gallery Women's National Republican Club Wood, Ward W. Woods, Edward F. Woods, Mrs. N.M. Woodstock Artists Association, Inc. Wood-Thomas, Alan Woodward, Harper Woodward, Maxwell Woodworth, Anna G. Woodworth Woodworth, Lillian Woodworth, Mrs. Stewart
  - "Woman's Day" - Woodworth (Box 68, Folder 0590A)
  - Worcester - Wyltwyck (Box 68, Folder 591)
    Worcester Art Museum Workman, Mrs. W.W. World Art Market Conference World's Fair Spanish Pavilion Worst, Gerhard Wright, Anne Wright, Frank C. Wright, Stella WSKG Public Television and Radio Wuerslin, Lothar H. Wuertz, Pauline N. Wuijster, C.C. Wulbern, Helen P. Wurz, Shirley Wyeth, Andrew Wyltwyck School
  - Washington, 1947, 1956-1957, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 592)
    Memoranda and correspondence re art at 2500 Foxhall Road.
  - Washington, 1947, 1956-1957, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 0592A)